unaided and So so he did this kind of
like amazing feat.
He walked either to the article the
Antarctic pole unaided and when
he got back he was completely bankrupt
and So
and also a bit of a nutter from what
I'm just going to tell you this so so
what
he did was he responded to being
completely bankrupt by Writing a
letter to John
Mills the actor Saying it's your fault
that I became an explorer
because I saw your films got the
Antarctic And that was the thing that
inspired
me to be an explorer and and now I'm
look at me I'm in trouble and like my
wife's
leaving me and like I'm I'm kind of
like completely in debt and everything
and
John John Mills replied by saying come
round for tea We start, you know, but
not as write your letters.
It's like it's a brave thing to do so
kind of a you went around to John
Mills
house of tea and and John Mills said,
okay, like you know, tell me what's
going
on And it's like, you know, I've got
all these debts and come what you know
I
mean all this kind of financial
trouble and living and John Mills said
We're
gonna have to talk you out He said no,
I can't I've talked to the banks.
I can't you know, they're not
listening He said no, no, no come in
the bathroom
So he said like they spent the rest of
the afternoon in the bathroom Putting
together a talk putting together an
inspirational talk Because like, you
know
John Mills is an actor And so he said
like, you know, this is what you're
gonna
do now you're gonna go around and talk
to people about walking to the
Antarctic
where it was and You that is gonna be
inspiring and you're going to make
money
and he said, you know, this is what I
do now I'm an after dinner speaker.
I'm an inspirational speaker and it's
all down to John Mills